<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<application>
 <id type="desktop">jbrout.desktop</id>
 <licence>CC BY-SA</licence>
 <name>JBrout</name>
 <summary>Photo manager which try to use standard EXIF/IPTC and XML to
     handle your photos</summary>
 <description>
     <p>jBrout is a photo manager, written in python/pygtk under the GPL
         licence. It's cross-platform, and has been tested on GNU/linux
         and windows XP/2k.</p>

     <p>The first jBrout was my first python application. I'd started to
         developp it because i was unable to find a “good application”
         to manage my collection of pictures. I'd tested a lot of
         well-known applications (adobe photoshop album, picasa, imatch,
         jasc photoalbum…) on windows. But no one was perfect (use of
         database (and often proprietary database), no respect for
         pictures, not cross-platforms (for future)…), so i've decided
         to build my own, and build &amp; use jBrout! Now, i've
         redevelopped jBrout 0.2.x from scratch! I manage more than
         30000 photos, with IPTC keywords, and i'm really happy …</p>

     <p>jBrout stands for J-Brout. “J” as JPEG, and “brout” as brouteur
         (a french world meanning “browser”). When I'd started this
         project google returned 0 pages pour the word “jbrout” ;-)</p>

     <p>jBrout doesn't use a database to handle your pictures! It just
         uses a XML file to handle your tags! The albums/pictures are
         managed like folders/files!!! All information that could be
         used in the interface are stored in your pictures.</p>

     <p>jBrout RESPECTS your pictures! it doesn't change any capital
         information in your pictures! (internal thumbnail are
         respected! rotation are loss-less…).</p>

     <p>jBrout is pluginable! In jBrout, Plugins are tools that can be
         applied on a set of pictures, or on an album. You can select one or
         more pictures, or an album, and call a plugin in the contextual
         menu.</p>
 </description>
 <screenshots>
     <screenshot type="default">http://jbrout.manatlan.com/jbrout/static/shot.png</screenshot>
 </screenshots>
 <url type="homepage">http://jbrout.manatlan.com/</url>
 <updatecontact>jbrout@googlegroups.com</updatecontact>
</application>
